const jokes = [
  { question: "What do hackers do on a boat?", answer: "Phishing." },
  {
    question: "Why was the IT guy in the hospital?",
    answer: "He touched the firewall.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why do app developers have such high insurance rates?",
    answer: "They're always crashing.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is it called when an IT person gets surgery on their fingers?",
    answer: "Tech knuckle support.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why do computers make such bad boxers?",
    answer: "Their bark is worse than their byte.",
  },
  {
    question: "Did you hear about the woman whose daughter adopted a baby?",
    answer: "Instagram.",
  },
  {
    question: "How does a computer get drunk?",
    answer: "It takes screenshots.",
  },
  {
    question: "Do you know the band 1023 megabytes?",
    answer: "They haven't had a gig yet.",
  },
  { question: "Who is a computer's favorite singer?", answer: "A Dell." },
  {
    question: "What's the best way to learn about computers?",
    answer: "Bit by bit.",
  },
  { question: "What is a computer's favorite animal?", answer: "A RAM." },
  {
    question: "Why did the PowerPoint presentation cross the road?",
    answer: "To get to the other slide.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why do people on Twitter tell me I'm always confused?",
    answer: "Because I don't follow.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why is everyone who works at the keyboard factory so rich?",
    answer: "They put in a lot of shifts.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why doesn't a computer's car last very long?",
    answer: "They always have hard drives.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why did the computer spy get fired?",
    answer: "She couldn't hack it.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What did the eyewitness tell the cops after a computer robbed a bank?",
    answer: "It went data way!",
  },
  { question: "Why are people afraid of computers?", answer: "They byte." },
  { question: "Where do naughty disk drives get sent?", answer: "Boot camp." },
  {
    question: "Why are spiders so good at the internet?",
    answer: "They know all the good web sites.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why do programmers never run the AC?",
    answer: "They prefer to open windows.",
  },
  {
    question: "What do computers do on a beach vacation?",
    answer: "Surf the net.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why did the man get so sad his computer had a virus?",
    answer: "It was a terminal illness.",
  },
  {
    question: "Why can't an IT guy keep a girlfriend?",
    answer: "He turns them all off and on again.",
  },
  { question: "Where do computers go to dance?", answer: "The disk-O." },
];

module.exports = { jokes };
